Hey everybody, we are joined by Milt
Hendrickson, the director of football
operations for the Green Bay Packers.
Welcome Milt, and in the third round,
you guys move up just a bit
to take Chris McLellan, a defensive
tackle out of Missouri. What did you
like about Chris? I think one of the
biggest things that stood out about
Chris through the whole process is that
every time you turned on SEC offenses
and they're playing against Missouri,
you always saw this guy out there and
I'm like, "Who is that?" Like, oh, there
he is. And he just like the second half
of the year and then through the
All-Star process and just the way he
just gradually kept stacking days and
just as a was just genuinely one [music]
of those guys that that rose through the
process. Now, he's got some nice
measurable, 6'4", 313, 5 flat 40. That's
all well and good, but the thing I want
to ask you about, he's got, Milt, 11-in
hands. Does he use those hands or what?
>> he's almost got you, Rock.
>> [laughter]
>> I think the the combination of obviously
his tag what you're you're you're
alluding to, but his arm length and hand
size, when he gets his hands on people,
he's able to create separation and then
move people.
>> There's no doubt. It's one of his
assets, absolutely. Now, could you talk
some about his play style? Do you Do you
see him as a run stuffer? Do you see him
as a pass rusher? Do you see him as a
penetrator tackle for loss guy? How do
you see him?
>> I think uh and it's
I think ultimately part of the reason we
valued him so much and and and you know,
ended up moving up to get him is that he
can do a lot of all of those things.
Um you can see him play the nose, you
can see him play the three tech, he can
play he can play big end. He's done a
nice job when he's had to hold the
point, but he's also one of those guys
to your point, you know, between his his
pressure and sack production, he's he's
a guy that he gets an edge, you know,
you you better you better account for
him in the passing game. Attitude and
culture
fit are important to you guys. How does
he fit in those regards? Uh I think he's
going to fit really, really well. He's
comes
Everything that we've gotten on him and
in our conversations with him and
getting to know him, he needs football.
And at the end of the day,
that's that's we're all here because we
need football. And he's he's one of
those guys that uh I'm very confident
will will hold that standard. Your
impressions of Brandon Zylstra, the
corner you drafted in the second round.
What do you like about him? He
desperately wanted to be a Green Bay
Packer.
>> Did he really? Yeah, he did. Yeah. No,
just just the conversations he had with
scouts uh through the whole process. But
at the end of the day, his play style
similar, you know, what we're talking
about with Chris, but just a just
[music] a
he's willing to tackle, he can cover, he
can put his hands on people and he's
just again, another guy that needs
football. You know, I've seen I've had a
chance to watch a little tape on him.
You said he's willing to tackle.
>> Yeah. I I think he'd prefer to tackle.
[laughter] I mean, he's always sticking
his nose in the rough stuff. Yeah, and
you know, the and the way, you know, we
don't scout and set the board for our,
you know, for our division, but you you
better be able to strap it up and, you
know, in the NFC North now.